(Leonard:)Here you go. Pad Thai, no peanuts.
(Howard:)Does it have peanut oil?
(Leonard:)I'm not sure.
(Leonard:)Everyone keep an eye on Howard
in case he starts to swell up.
(Sheldon:)Since it's not bee season,
you can have my epinephrine.
(Raj:)- Any chopsticks?
- Don't need chopsticks, this is Thai food.
(Leonard:)Here we go.
(Sheldon:)Thailand has had the fork
since the latter half of the 19th century.
They don't put the fork in their mouth,
they use it to put the food on a spoon...
(Sheldon:)...which then goes into their mouth.
(Leonard:)Ask him for a napkin, I dare you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Leonard:)I'll get it.
(Howard:)Do I look puffy? I feel puffy.
- Hey, Leonard.
- Oh, hi, Penny.
- Am I interrupting?
- No.
SHELDON:
You're not swelling, Howard.
HOWARD: No, look at my fingers,
they're like Vienna sausages.
- Sounds like you have company.
- They're not going anywhere.
(Leonard:)So you're coming home from work.
That's great. How was work?
You know, it's a Cheesecake Factory...
(Penny:)...people order cheesecake
and I bring it to them.
So you kind of act
as like a carbohydrate delivery system?